so adjusted rates.
And then in your mind,
is HS or MS likely a bigger indication?
Thank you.
Yeah, I mean, I think I don't know
if I have the details, Sachin,
that we may have to follow up with you
on our expectations on the phase three study
of the design in HS.
But I would still say it's all really going to depend
in terms of your second part of your question,
the overall data profile that we see.
I think clearly if Remy and MS
proves itself both in relapse rate
and disability progression to be better
than the anti-CD20s,
then of course the opportunity here is massive.
I think if it's in line
or ultimately a little bit worse,
then I think HS could be a similarly sized indication.
And we know the HS market is growing.
We've guided it to be a 5 billion market growing.
Certainly the petition potential
is there to be much larger.
And it might be that a safe and effective oral option
would be required.
But I think it's going to be really, really attractive.
So I think it's really going to be dependent
on that MS readout to understand the size
of the MS opportunity.
But I think it's exciting that we have two shots on goal
with Remy to add to what's two already very compelling
indications that we have going forward.
But we'll get back to you on your question on HS.
Next question.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Richard Foster
from JPMorgan.
Please go ahead.
Hi.
Thanks for taking my question.
A question about China.
You reference competition for Cosentix,
but we also saw much lower growth in general in China
across Q1, despite the strong start for Lecveo.
So should we expect more slower international growth
for Entresto, Cosentix going forward,
and slower overall China development?
Or can Lecveo continue to drag China growth to double digits?
And I have one question.
I have one quick linked question on Lecveo.
How much of a peak do you think can come from China,
given the strong start?
Thanks very much.
Yeah.
Thanks, Richard.
So overall, the dynamics in China,
we've seen a stabilization in the early part of this year.
I don't think we're back to the pre-2025 growth levels,
but we do see a stabilization overall in the market
as well and in our key segments.
And so we feel confident that our China business can be in that high, single,